Guide to the William Benton Papers 1839-1973
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: General Files
  - Subseries 5: Foreign Affairs
    - Sub-subseries 3: UNESCO
      - Sub-sub-subseries 2: 1958-1973
        - Issues, 1963 (Box 394, Folder 1)
        - Issues, 1964 (Box 394, Folder 2)
        - Issues, 1965 (Box 394, Folder 3)
        - Issues, 1966 (Box 394, Folder 4)
        - Issues, 1967 (Box 394, Folder 5)
        - Issues, 1968 (Box 394, Folder 6)
        - Issues, general, #1 (Box 395, Folder 1)
        - Issues, general, #2 (Box 395, Folder 2)
        - Issues, general, #3 (Box 395, Folder 3)
        - Lists, #1 (Box 395, Folder 4)
        - Lists, #2 (Box 395, Folder 5)
        - Kotschnig, Walter, 1963-1965 (Box 395, Folder 6)
        - Kotschnig, 1966-1968 (Box 395, Folder 7)
        - Maheu, Rene, 1963-1965 (Box 395, Folder 8)
        - Maheu, 1966-1968 (Box 395, Folder 9)
        - Maheu, 1970-1973 (Box 395, Folder 10)
        - Mass communications (Box 396, Folder 1)
        - Meetings, general (Box 396, Folder 2)
        - Meetings, Executive Board, 1963-1964 (Box 396, Folder 3)
        - Meetings, Executive Board, 1965-1966 (Box 396, Folder 4)
        - Meetings, Executive Board, 1967-1968 (Box 396, Folder 5)
        - Meetings, National Commission, Chicago, 1963 (Box 396, Folder 6)
        - Meetings, National Commission, 1963 (Box 396, Folder 7)
        - Meetings, National Commission, 1964 (Box 396, Folder 8)
        - Meetings, National Commission, 1965 (Box 396, Folder 9)
        - Meetings, National Commission, 1966 (Box 397, Folder 1)
        - Meetings, National Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 397, Folder 2)
        - Member states, general, 1963-1964 (Box 397, Folder 3)
        - Member states, general, 1965-1966 (Box 397, Folder 4)
        - Member states, general, 1967-1968 (Box 397, Folder 5)
        - Member states, A-H, miscellaneous (Box 397, Folder 6)
        - Member states, Brazil (Box 397, Folder 7)
        - Member states, I-M, miscellaneous (Box 397, Folder 8)
        - Member states, Morocco (Box 397, Folder 9)
        - Member states, N-O, miscellaneous (Box 398, Folder 1)
        - Member states, P-Z, miscellaneous (Box 398, Folder 2)
        - Member states, U.S.S.R. (Box 398, Folder 3)
        - Member states, United Kingdom (Box 398, Folder 4)
        - N-Z, general (Box 398, Folder 5)
        - National Commission, 1963 (Box 398, Folder 6)
        - National Commission, 1964 (Box 398, Folder 7)
        - National Commission, 1965 (Box 398, Folder 8)
        - National Commission, 1966 (Box 398, Folder 9)
        - National Commission, 1967-1968 (Box 398, Folder 10)
        - National Commission, appointments, 1964-1966 (Box 398, Folder 11)
        - National Commission, appointments, 1967-1968 (Box 398, Folder 12)
        - National Commission, Branscomb, Harvie (Box 399, Folder 1)
        - National Commission, public relations (Box 399, Folder 2)
        - Otetea, Andrei, 1969-1971 (Box 399, Folder 3)
        - Personal, general (Box 399, Folder 4)
        - Personal, Crillon suite (Box 399, Folder 5)
        - Personal, personnel (Box 399, Folder 6)
        - Population control (Box 399, Folder 7)
        - Projects, general, 1964-1966 (Box 399, Folder 8)
        - Projects, general, 1967 (Box 399, Folder 9)
        - Projects, general, 1968 (Box 399, Folder 10)
        - Projects, Bellagio meeting (Box 399, Folder 11)
        - Projects, field offices, 1964-1965 (Box 400, Folder 1)
        - Projects, field offices, 1966-1968 (Box 400, Folder 2)
        - Projects, Florence-Beirut agreement (Box 400, Folder 3)
        - Projects, Ford Foundation (Box 400, Folder 4)
        - Projects, Freedom of Information Conference (Box 400, Folder 5)
        - Projects, Haussamen, Crane, #1 (Box 400, Folder 6)
        - Projects, Haussamen, #2 (Box 400, Folder 7)
        - Projects, human rights (Roosevelt Foundation), 1963 (Box 400, Folder 8)
        - Projects, human rights (Roosevelt Foundation), 1964 (Box 400, Folder 9)
        - Projects, management survey (Box 400, Folder 10)
        - Projects, Rome center (Box 400, Folder 11)
        - Projects, Task Force (Box 401, Folder 1)
        - Public relations, general, 1963 (Box 401, Folder 2)
        - Public relations, general, 1964 (Box 401, Folder 3)
        - Public relations, general, 1965 (Box 401, Folder 4)
        - Public relations, general, 1966 (Box 401, Folder 5)
        - Public relations, general, 1967 (Box 401, Folder 6)
        - Public relations, general, 1968 (Box 401, Folder 7)
        - Public relations, American Embassy (Paris) (Box 401, Folder 8)
        - Public relations, Britannica (Box 401, Folder 9)
        - Public relations, British officials (Box 402, Folder 1)
        - Public relations, classified documents (Box 402, Folder 2)
        - Public relations, ideas and criticisms (Box 402, Folder 3)
        - Public relations, miscellaneous, #1 (Box 402, Folder 4)
        - Public relations, miscellaneous, #2 (Box 402, Folder 5)
        - Public relations, miscellaneous, #3 (Box 402, Folder 6)
        - Public relations, United Nations, 1963-1965 (Box 402, Folder 7)
        - Public relations, United Nations, 1966-1968 (Box 402, Folder 8)
        - Public relations, U. S. Congress (Box 402, Folder 9)
        - Publications, 1964 (Box 403, Folder 1)
        - Publications, 1965-1966 (Box 403, Folder 2)
        - Publicity, 1963-1965 (Box 403, Folder 3)
        - Publicity, 1966-1968 (Box 403, Folder 4)
        - Schramm, Wilbur (Box 403, Folder 5)
        - Secretariat, general, 1963-1964 (Box 403, Folder 6)
        - Secretariat, general, 1965-1966 (Box 403, Folder 7)
        - Secretariat, general, 1967-1968 (Box 403, Folder 8)
        - Secretariat, applicants, 1963-1964 (Box 403, Folder 9)
        - Secretariat, applicants, 1965 (Box 404, Folder 1)
        - Secretariat, applicants, 1966 (Box 404, Folder 2)
        - Secretariat, applicants, 1967 (Box 404, Folder 3)
        - Secretariat, applicants, 1968 (Box 404, Folder 4)
        - Secretariat, applicants, miscellaneous (Box 404, Folder 5)
        - Social engagements, 1963-1964 (Box 404, Folder 6)
        - Social engagements, 1965-1968 (Box 405, Folder 1)
        - Travels, general (Box 405, Folder 2)
        - Travels, Africa, 1964, #1 (Box 405, Folder 3)
        - Travels, Africa, #2 (Box 405, Folder 4)
        - Travels, Europe (Box 405, Folder 5)
        - Travels, Mexico (Box 405, Folder 6)
        - U. N. Development Program (Box 405, Folder 7)
        - U. S. delegation, general, 1963 (Box 405, Folder 8)
        - U. S. delegation, general, 1964 (Box 405, Folder 9)
        - U. S. delegation, general, 1965 (Box 405, Folder 10)
        - U. S. delegation, general, 1966 (Box 406, Folder 1)
        - U. S. delegation, general, 1967 (Box 406, Folder 2)
        - U. S. delegation, general, 1968 (Box 406, Folder 3)
        - U. S. delegation, applicants, 1963-1966 (Box 406, Folder 4)
        - U. S. delegation, applicants, 1967-1968 (Box 406, Folder 5)
        - U. S. delegation, appointments (Box 406, Folder 6)
        - U. S. delegation, Cleveland, Harlan (Box 406, Folder 7)
        - U. S. delegation, Frankel, Charles (Box 406, Folder 8)
        - U. S. delegation, Haussaman, Crane (Box 406, Folder 9)
        - U. S. delegation, miscellaneous, A-C (Box 407, Folder 1)
        - U. S. delegation, miscellaneous, D-L (Box 407, Folder 2)
        - U. S. delegation, miscellaneous, M-R (Box 407, Folder 3)
        - U. S. delegation, miscellaneous, S-Z (Box 407, Folder 4)
        - U. S. delegation, policy, 1965-1966 (Box 407, Folder 5)
        - U. S. delegation, policy, 1967-1968 (Box 407, Folder 6)
        - U. S. delegation, voting (Box 407, Folder 7)
        - U. S. delegation, Wade, Robert, 1963 (Box 407, Folder 8)
        - U. S. delegation, Wade, 1964 (Box 407, Folder 9)
        - U. S. delegation, Wade, 1965 (Box 407, Folder 10)
        - U. S. delegation, Wade, 1966 (Box 407, Folder 11)
        - U. S. delegation, Wade, 1967-1968 (Box 407, Folder 12)
  - Subseries 6: Education and Philanthropy
    - Sub-subseries 1: University of Chicago
      - Sub-sub-subseries 1: 1948-1957
        - A-B, general (Box 408, Folder 1)
        - Bell, Laird, 1948-1957 (Box 408, Folder 2)
        - Blair, William McCormick (Box 408, Folder 3)
        - Ca-Cl, general (Box 408, Folder 4)
        - Cleveland Conference (Box 408, Folder 5)
        - Co-Cz, general (Box 408, Folder 6)
        - D, general (Box 408, Folder 7)
        - E-F, general (Box 408, Folder 8)
        - G-H, general (Box 408, Folder 9)
        - Hall, J. Parker (Box 408, Folder 10)
        - J-L, general (Box 409, Folder 1)
        - Kimpton, Lawrence A. (Box 409, Folder 2)
        - M-O, general (Box 409, Folder 3)
        - Morgenstern, William (Box 409, Folder 4)
        - P-Q, general (Box 409, Folder 5)
        - Paepcke, Walter (Box 409, Folder 6)
        - Probst, George (Box 409, Folder 7)
        - R, general (Box 409, Folder 8)
        - Sa-Sh, general (Box 409, Folder 9)
        - Si-Sz, general (Box 410, Folder 1)
        - Smith, Hermon D. (Box 410, Folder 2)
        - Stutzman, Frances (Box 410, Folder 3)
        - Swift, Harold (Box 410, Folder 4)
        - T-Z, general (Box 410, Folder 5)
        - Tyler, Ralph W. (Box 410, Folder 6)
        - Williams, Lynn A. (Box 410, Folder 7)
        - Zimmerman, Herbert P. (Box 410, Folder 8)
      - Sub-sub-subseries 2: 1958-1973
        - A-Z, general (Box 411, Folder 1)
        - Axelson, C. F., 1962-1971 (Box 411, Folder 2)
        - Beadle, George and Muriel, 1968-1972 (Box 411, Folder 3)
        - Blair, William McCormick, 1958-1972 (Box 411, Folder 4)
        - Cone, Fairfax, 1958-1971 (Box 411, Folder 5)
        - D-M, general (Box 411, Folder 6)
        - Nef, John, 1958-1973 (Box 411, Folder 7)
        - S, general (Box 411, Folder 8)
        - Schultz, Theodore (Box 411, Folder 9)
        - Stutzman, Frances, 1958-1965 (Box 411, Folder 10)
        - Stutzman, 1968-1972 (Box 411, Folder 11)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Benton Foundation
      - American Assembly, general, 1958-1959 (Box 412, Folder 1)
      - American Assembly, general, 1960-1961 (Box 412, Folder 2)
      - American Assembly, general, 1962-1964 (Box 412, Folder 3)
      - American Assembly, general, 1965-1966 (Box 412, Folder 4)
      - American Assembly, general, 1967-1968 (Box 412, Folder 5)
      - American Assembly, general, 1969-1971 (Box 412, Folder 6)
      - American Assembly, general, 1972-1973 (Box 412, Folder 7)
      - American Assembly, broadcasting program, 1964-1970 (Box 412, Folder 8)
      - American Assembly, Board of Trustees, 1958-1960 (Box 413, Folder 1)
      - American Assembly, Board of Trustees, 1961-1963 (Box 413, Folder 2)
      - American Assembly, Board of Trustees, 1964-1966 (Box 413, Folder 3)
      - American Assembly, Board of Trustees, 1967-1968 (Box 413, Folder 4)
      - American Assembly, Board of Trustees, 1969 (Box 413, Folder 5)
      - American Assembly, Board of Trustees, 1970-1972 (Box 413, Folder 6)
      - American Assembly, fund raising and contributions, 1958 (Box 413, Folder 7)
      - American Assembly, fund raising and contributions, 1959-1962 (Box 413, Folder 8)
      - American Assembly, fund raising and contributions, 1963-1964 (Box 414, Folder 1)
      - American Assembly, fund raising and contributions, 1965 (Box 414, Folder 2)
      - American Assembly, fund raising and contributions, 1966 (Box 414, Folder 3)
      - American Assembly, fund raising and contributions, 1967-1972 (Box 414, Folder 4)
      - American Assembly, lists, releases and publications, 1959-1962 (Box 414, Folder 5)
      - American Assembly, lists, 1963-1964 (Box 414, Folder 6)
      - American Assembly, lists, 1966-1968 (Box 414, Folder 7)
      - American Assembly, lists, 1969-1972 (Box 414, Folder 8)
      - American Committee on United Europe, 1958-1960 (Box 415, Folder 1)
      - American Foreign Service Association, #1 (Box 415, Folder 2)
      - American Foreign Service Association, #2 (Box 415, Folder 3)
      - American Foreign Service Association, #3 (Box 415, Folder 4)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1958 (Box 416, Folder 1)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1959 (Box 416, Folder 2)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1960 (Box 416, Folder 3)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1961 (Box 416, Folder 4)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1962 (Box 416, Folder 5)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1963-1964 (Box 416, Folder 6)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1965 (Box 416, Folder 7)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1966 (Box 416, Folder 8)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1967-1968 (Box 416, Folder 9)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1969-1970 (Box 416, Folder 10)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, general, 1971-1973 (Box 416, Folder 11)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, 1958-1960 (Box 417, Folder 1)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, Yale merger proposal, 1960-1962 (Box 417, Folder 2)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, 1961-1962 (Box 417, Folder 3)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, 1963-1965 (Box 417, Folder 4)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, 1966 (Box 417, Folder 5)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, 1967 (Box 417, Folder 6)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 417, Folder 7)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, 1969-1970 (Box 417, Folder 8)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, 1971 (Box 417, Folder 9)
      - American Shakespeare Festival, Board of Trustees, 1972-1973 (Box 417, Folder 10)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, 1958-1959 (Box 418, Folder 1)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, 1960-1961 (Box 418, Folder 2)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, Jan.-June 1962 (Box 418, Folder 3)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, July-Dec. 1962 (Box 418, Folder 4)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, 1963 (Box 418, Folder 5)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, Jan.-June 1964 (Box 418, Folder 6)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, July-Dec. 1964 (Box 418, Folder 7)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, 1965 (Box 418, Folder 8)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, 1966 (Box 418, Folder 9)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, 1967 (Box 419, Folder 1)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, 1968-1969 (Box 419, Folder 2)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, Feb.-May 1970 (Box 419, Folder 3)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, June-Dec. 1970 (Box 419, Folder 4)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, Jan.-May 1971 (Box 419, Folder 5)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, June 1971-May 1972 (Box 419, Folder 6)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, June-Aug. 1972 (Box 419, Folder 7)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, general, Sept.-Dec. 1972 (Box 419, Folder 8)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Board of Trustees, 1959-1960 (Box 420, Folder 1)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Board of Trustees, 1961-1962 (Box 420, Folder 2)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Board of Trustees, 1963-1964 (Box 420, Folder 3)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Board of Trustees, 1965 (Box 420, Folder 4)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Board of Trustees, 1966-1967 (Box 420, Folder 5)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Board of Trustees, 1968-1969 (Box 420, Folder 6)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Board of Trustees, 1970 (Box 420, Folder 7)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Board of Trustees, 1971-1973 (Box 420, Folder 8)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, contributions, 1959-1967 (Box 420, Folder 9)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Aspen College proposal, 1962-1963 (Box 420, Folder 10)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Aspen College proposal, 1964-1965 (Box 420, Folder 11)
      - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, Aspen College proposal, 1966-1970 (Box 420, Folder 12)
      - Brandeis University, general, 1958-1962 (Box 421, Folder 1)
      - Brandeis University, general, 1963 (Box 421, Folder 2)
      - Brandeis University, general, 1964-1966 (Box 421, Folder 3)
      - Brandeis University, general, 1965-1967, Stevenson memorial (Box 421, Folder 4)
      - Brandeis University, general, 1967 (Box 421, Folder 5)
      - Brandeis University, general, 1968 (Box 421, Folder 6)
      - Brandeis University, general, 1969-1970 (Box 421, Folder 7)
      - Brandeis University, general, 1971-1972 (Box 421, Folder 8)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1961 (Box 422, Folder 1)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1962 (Box 422, Folder 2)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1963 (Box 422, Folder 3)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1964 (Box 422, Folder 4)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1965 (Box 422, Folder 5)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1966 (Box 422, Folder 6)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1967 (Box 422, Folder 7)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 422, Folder 8)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1969 (Box 422, Folder 9)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1970 (Box 422, Folder 10)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1971 (Box 423, Folder 1)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, 1972-1973 (Box 423, Folder 2)
      - Brandeis University, Board of Trustees, minutes, 1972 (Box 423, Folder 3)
      - Brandeis University, contributions and fund raising, 1961-1964 (Box 423, Folder 4)
      - Brandeis University, contributions and fund raising, 1965-1968 (Box 423, Folder 5)
      - Brandeis University, contributions and fund raising, 1969-1972 (Box 423, Folder 6)
      - Brandeis University, events and activities, 1961-1964 (Box 423, Folder 7)
      - Brandeis University, events and activities, 1965-1967 (Box 423, Folder 8)
      - Brandeis University, events and activities, 1968 (Box 423, Folder 9)
      - Brandeis University, events and activities, 1969-1970 (Box 423, Folder 10)
      - Brandeis University, events and activities, 1971-1972 (Box 423, Folder 11)
      - Business Committee for the Arts, Inc., 1970-1971 (Box 424, Folder 1)
      - Business Committee for the Arts, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 424, Folder 2)
      - Carleton College, general, 1958-1959 (Box 424, Folder 3)
      - Carleton College, general, 1960-1961 (Box 424, Folder 4)
      - Carleton College, Board of Trustees, 1958-1961 (Box 424, Folder 5)
      - Carleton College, contributions and fund raising, 1959-1961 (Box 424, Folder 6)
      - Carleton College, administration and policy, 1958-1960 (Box 424, Folder 7)
      - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, general, 1959 (Box 424, Folder 8)
      - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, general, 1960 (Box 424, Folder 9)
      - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, general, 1961-1964 (Box 424, Folder 10)
      - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, general, 1965-1967 (Box 424, Folder 11)
      - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, The Center Club, 1965-1970 (Box 424, Folder 12)
      - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, general, 1968-1971 (Box 424, Folder 13)
      - Cleveland Conference, 1958 (Box 425, Folder 1)
      - Cleveland Conference, 1959 (Box 425, Folder 2)
      - Cleveland Conference, 1960 (Box 425, Folder 3)
      - Cleveland Conference, 1961 (Box 425, Folder 4)
      - Cleveland Conference, 1962-1964 (Box 425, Folder 5)
      - Cleveland Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 425, Folder 6)
      - Cleveland Conference, 1967-1970 (Box 425, Folder 7)
      - Cleveland Conference, 1971-1973 (Box 425, Folder 8)
      - Commission on the Frame of Government, 1968 (Box 426, Folder 1)
      - Commission on the Frame of Government, 1969 (Box 426, Folder 2)
      - Commission on the Frame of Government, 1969, Zwick memorandum (Box 426, Folder 3)
      - Commission on the Press, general, 1957-1959 (Box 426, Folder 4)
      - Commission on the Press, Gould, Bruce and Luce, Harry, 1960-1961 (Box 426, Folder 5)
      - Commission on the Press, Markel, Lester and Shep Stone, 1959-1961 (Box 426, Folder 6)
      - Commission on the Press, affiliate institutions, 1960-1961 (Box 426, Folder 7)
      - Commission on the Press, affiliate institutions, 1962 (Box 426, Folder 8)
      - Commission on the Press, affiliate institutions, 1963 (Box 426, Folder 9)
      - Commission on the Press, affiliate institutions, 1964-1968 (Box 426, Folder 10)
      - Commission on the Press, finance, 1959-1965 (Box 426, Folder 11)
      - Commission on the Press, progress reports, 1961-1963 (Box 426, Folder 12)
      - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1961-1962 (Box 427, Folder 1)
      - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1963 (Box 427, Folder 2)
      - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1964-1966 (Box 427, Folder 3)
      - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1967-1968 (Box 427, Folder 4)
      - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1969 (Box 427, Folder 5)
      - Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1971-1972 (Box 427, Folder 6)
      - Committee for the Preservation of the White House, 1964 (Box 428, Folder 1)
      - Committee for the Preservation of the White House, 1965 (Box 428, Folder 2)
      - Committee for the Preservation of the White House, 1965, Webster portrait acquisition (Box 428, Folder 3)
      - Committee for the Preservation of the White House, 1966 (Box 428, Folder 4)
      - Committee for the Preservation of the White House, 1967 (Box 428, Folder 5)
      - Committee for the Preservation of the White House, 1968-1969 (Box 428, Folder 6)
      - Congressional Awards, 1958-1960 (Box 428, Folder 7)
      - Congressional Awards, 1961-1963 (Box 428, Folder 8)
      - Congressional Awards, 1964-1967 (Box 428, Folder 9)
      - Congressional Awards, 1968-1972 (Box 428, Folder 10)
      - Democratic Advisory Council, 1958 (Box 429, Folder 1)
      - Democratic Advisory Council, 1959 (Box 429, Folder 2)
      - Democratic Advisory Council, 1960-1961 (Box 429, Folder 3)
      - Fair Campaign Practices Committee, Inc., 1958-1965 (Box 429, Folder 4)
      - Fair Campaign Practices Committee, Inc., 1966-1970 (Box 429, Folder 5)
      - Fair Campaign Practices Committee, Inc., 1971-1973 (Box 429, Folder 6)
      - Foreign Relations Committee Testimony, planning and development, 1958 (Box 429, Folder 7)
      - Foreign Relations Committee Testimony, planning and development, post-project data, 1958 (Box 429, Folder 8)
      - Hampton Institute, general, 1958 (Box 430, Folder 1)
      - Hampton Institute, general, 1959-1961 (Box 430, Folder 2)
      - Hampton Institute, general, 1962-1967 (Box 430, Folder 3)
      - Hampton Institute, general, 1968 (Box 430, Folder 4)
      - Hampton Institute, general, 1969-1972 (Box 430, Folder 5)
      - Hampton Institute, Board of Trustees, 1958-1961 (Box 430, Folder 6)
      - Hampton Institute, Board of Trustees, 1962-1965 (Box 430, Folder 7)
      - Hampton Institute, contributions and fund raising, 1960-1964 (Box 430, Folder 8)
      - Institute of International Education, general, 1962 (Box 431, Folder 1)
      - Institute of International Education, general, 1963 (Box 431, Folder 2)